classi4u.com 2017-11-02

# Privacy Policy | Classi4U.com

Classi4U has established its privacy policy to explain how your information within the purview of Classi4U is protected, collected and used. This policy may be updated by Classi4U. Classi4U will post notices of its policy changes on the Classi4U site at: <http://www.classi4u.com/classiprivacy.php>. You must review the policy on a regular basis to keep yourself apprised of any changes. 

**PRIVACY PROTECTION**

Classi4U does not share your information with third parties for marketing purposes, or engage in cross-marketing or link-referral programs with other similar sites. Classi4U recommends its customers to keep their password safe and do not remember it on public (shared) computers (Internet-cafe, college, library, family computer etc). Classi4U does not knowingly collect any information from persons under the age of 13. If Classi4U learns that a posting is by a person under the age of 13, Classi4U will remove that posting. Classi4U, or persons who post on Classi4U, may provide links to third party websites, with different privacy policies. Classi4U is not responsible for, nor have any control over, those third party websites. 

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**

Classi4U collect traditional contact information such as your name, mailing and/or billing address, phone number and email address for few purposes: to send selfpublishing and confirmation emails, to authenticate user accounts, to provide subscription email services, to register for forums, to process any credit card charges, etc.

Your personal information may be collected by Classi4U if you provide it in the feedback or comments, post it on our classifieds or other publishing areas of the website.

Should you expect your personal information to be private please do not post any personal information on Classi4U site. Standard web log entries for each page served, including visitor´s IP address, page URL, and timestamp are collected by Classi4U web logs in order to help diagnose problem with Classi4U servers, to administer Classi4U site, and to otherwise enhance visitor´s use of Classi4U sites and services. 

**COOKIES**

Classi4U.com set and use cookies to enhance your user experience, such as remembering your personal settings. The user may choose to disable, adjust enabled cookies or delete cookies by configuring the web browser. But it may result in the unavailability of some functions and features in this website. This website will not share any personal information with third parties. 

Advertisements appearing on this web site may set and access cookies on your computer and is subject to the privacy policy of those parties providing the advertisement.     
Third party plugins used for authentication and social media sharing may set and access cookies on your computer and is subject to the privacy policy of those parties providing the service.  
We use Google Analytics which collects visitor activity anonymously, to help us to know how vistors use our site. For Google Analytics privacy policy and to find out how to opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites you use, visit this [Google page](https://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/learn/privacy.html).

 **DATA STORAGE**

Classi4U stores in its database all user generated content (classified ads, forums, guestbook postings etc.) even after they are deleted, as well as can archive such data elsewhere. Classi4U indefinitely stores web logs and other records. Registered members can access and update personal account information through the account homepage. 

**DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Classi4U may disclose information about its users if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. Classi4U may also disclose information about its users to law enforcement officers or others, in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms of Use; respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third-party; or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Classi4U, its users or the general public. Classi4U complies with the provisions of C.R.S. § 6-1-716 pertinent to the breaches of security notifications effective September 1st, 2006. 

**GLOBAL USE**

By providing us with data and by visiting Classi4U you acknowledge and agree that due to the global use of Classi4U we may use the data collected in the course of your use of our site and/or services for the purposes identified in this policy or in our other communications to you, including the transmission of information outside your resident jurisdiction. Data provided to Classi4U may be stored on servers throughout different jurisdictions. User agrees to consent to transfer of such data to different locations. 

**IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH CLASSI4U PRIVACY POLICY PLEASE STOP USING THE SERVICE.**
